<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>stderr | log</title>
 <link href="http://stderr.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://stderr.me"/>
 <updated>2013-05-17T19:46:39-04:00</updated>
 <id>http://stderr.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Jason Mitchell</name>
   <email>jason.j.mitchell+myspambin@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Moving to Arch?</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/04/16/way-of-the-arch/"/>
   <updated>2013-04-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/04/16/way-of-the-arch</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A few months back I installed Ubuntu; shortly after that I moved to CrunchBang. For the most part I’ve enjoyed my experiences with CruncBang. The few things I haven’t enjoyed where directly related to it foundation, Debian. However, I stuck with it and even upgraded the Macbook (4,1) replacing the HD with an SSD and doubling the RAM.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I enjoyed the experience even more. Yet I keep feeling like the Debian base was holding me back. My use cases don’t require stability. For the last week I’ve been tinkering with ArchLinux. First in a VM, then finally my older MacBook (2,1). The biggest headache to date, and I’m sure many more will come, has been the ability to boot the system. I was using the install CD as a bootstrap. Three days ago I started learning, more like glossing over, how EFI booting works. Slowly I was able to build a semi-working boot system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main important parts /boot/efi must be its own volume
mkdir -p /boot/efi/EFI/boot&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;install refind and move the required bits over to /boot/efi/EFI/boot rename refind_ia32.efi to bootia32.efi (the 2,1 MacBook has a 32-bit efi) and your now able to boot into refind.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Registered</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/04/08/dopey-register/"/>
   <updated>2013-04-08T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/04/08/dopey-register</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been going back and forth over this for the last week. I really want to do the the Wine &amp;amp; Dine for the 4th year in a row, I really want to tackle the Dopey Challenge. I only have the ability to do one of the weekends. I also don’t know if this how I wanted to spend a weeks vacation. In the end the bigger regret would be not doing the Dopey Challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I took advantage to the Disney Visa pre-registration offer and discount, only saving me $15 ;(&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Shameful</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/27/why-turbotax-hates-you/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/27/why-turbotax-hates-you</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>forecast.io</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/27/weather/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/27/weather</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I just love the work the guys at &lt;a href=&quot;http://darkskyapp.com/&quot;&gt;Dark Sky&lt;/a&gt; have done. They now have a great, yes great, WebApp forcast.io with a nifty API. I’ve spent a good portion of my day playing with it learning a bit about ruby and json.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Spring Spruce</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/24/spring-fresh/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-24T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/24/spring-fresh</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Spring is in the air and I’ve been feeling the need to give the site a bit more personality. Currently I’m working on matching a few fonts together that should help shape the look and feel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this I choose to look at the Google Web Fonts (maybe I should look at Font Squirrel next), it seemed to provide the best way to get ensure my choices would be available to all visitors of the site. Right now I’m enamored with four unique fonts Arvo, Kameron, Overlock and Sintony. The mix of these four does seem a bit disjointed right now. I wonder what will make the cut.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Heigh-Ho! Heigh-Ho!</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/23/dopey-challenge/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/23/dopey-challenge</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;My 2013 goal was to complete the Goofy, and I meet my goal. I was nearly sure I would running the Goofy in 2014 as I felt I could have done better. Now Disney has announced the Dopey Challenge; 5K, 10K, Half Marathon and Marathon for a whopping 48.6 miles for 6 medals. I think I now have a new challenge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My room is booked.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Apollo-Era Rocket Engines Pulled From The Sea</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/21/apollo/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/21/apollo</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I just love the underwater photos.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Running 2012</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/20/the-2012/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/20/the-2012</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I started writing this on my plane trip back home from Florida after completing my first marathon in January. It sat in my draft folder, and sat some more. This time I will publish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2012 I ran the Chicago Rock ‘n’ Roll Half along with the Walt Disney World Wine and Dine. The Chicago Rock ‘n Roll went far better than I could have expected, while the Wine &amp;amp; Dine went far worse than I could have imagined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My official &lt;a href=&quot;http://running.competitor.com/cgiresults?eId=43&quot;&gt;Rock ‘n’ Roll Chicago&lt;/a&gt; time(s)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5K – 32:59&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10K – 1:06:36&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10 Mile – 1:48:48&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Half Marathon – 2:24:39&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My official &lt;a href=&quot;http://results.active.com/events/2012-disney-wine-dine-half-marathon--2013&quot;&gt;Wine &amp;amp; Dine&lt;/a&gt; time(s)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;5K – 29:46&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;10K – 1:10:09&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;15K in 1:48:14&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Half Marathon – 2:43:56&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>NoPriv.py</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/18/imap-backup/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-18T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/18/imap-backup</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I could have used a script like this a few months back when I was trying to figure out what to do with my email hosting issues.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>An Update</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2013/03/16/an-update/"/>
   <updated>2013-03-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2013/03/16/an-update</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I must admit I haven’t said much in some time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve nearly migrated my full computer usage from my Mini running OS X to my old MacBook running &lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/&quot;&gt;CrunchBang Linux&lt;/a&gt;, with a few modificatons. So far I’m liking the switch. Not because its free or any such ideology. This set up is must less computing intensive, and I feel like I’m living closer to the hardware. It a way I feel more conected with the technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also started to use &lt;a href=&quot;http://sparkleshare.org/&quot;&gt;SparkleShare&lt;/a&gt; more than DropBox, moved my email to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastmail.fm&quot;&gt;FastMail&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Linux Playground</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/11/23/linux-playground/"/>
   <updated>2012-11-23T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/11/23/linux-playground</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been playing with Linux on two old Macbooks (4,1 and 2,1). The 4,1 system has Ubuntu while the 2,1 system is running Crunchbang. To me the stock Ubuntu install is a bit to much for me, and I much prefer the Crunchbang install. However I have EFI boot issues with the CB install.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here are a few quick links:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.gnome.org/diegoe/2012/11/16/efi-mode-boot-on-macbook31-with-debian/&quot;&gt;http://blogs.gnome.org/diegoe/2012/11/16/efi-mode-boot-on-macbook31-with-debian/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kcore.org/?menumain=4&amp;amp;menusub=3&quot;&gt;http://www.kcore.org/?menumain=4&amp;amp;menusub=3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thinkwiki.org/wiki/UEFI_Firmware&quot;&gt;http://www.thinkwiki.org/wiki/UEFI_Firmware&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/forums/viewtopic.php?id=21510&quot;&gt;http://crunchbang.org/forums/viewtopic.php?id=21510&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.realcomputerguy.com/2012/05/efi-stub-booting-without-bootloader.html&quot;&gt;http://blog.realcomputerguy.com/2012/05/efi-stub-booting-without-bootloader.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Unified_Extensible_Firmware_Interface&quot;&gt;https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Unified_Extensible_Firmware_Interface&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wiki.debian.org/MacBook&quot;&gt;http://wiki.debian.org/MacBook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://forums.debian.net/viewtopic.php?f=16&amp;amp;t=81120&quot;&gt;http://forums.debian.net/viewtopic.php?f=16&amp;amp;t=81120&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wiki.osdev.org/GRUB&quot;&gt;http://wiki.osdev.org/GRUB&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://crunchbang.org/forums/viewtopic.php?id=10755&quot;&gt;http://crunchbang.org/forums/viewtopic.php?id=10755&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;grub-efi-amd64 is also a useful package’s… I think.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The other social</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/10/04/the-other-social/"/>
   <updated>2012-10-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/10/04/the-other-social</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I was never a Facebook fan. I get the general point of the service to easily stay connected to friends and family. However maybe its because I’m not an overly social person, I never understood why so many people view the internet thru Facebook, or buy so heavily into the Facebook services. As a result I was more of a Twitter users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve preferred Twitter to Facebook because it had an open feeling. Something more noble where the service was “we the people.” Slowly that feeling is melting away. Many of the geek thought leaders have started looking else where. One of the first attempts at replacing Twitter was &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Identi.ca&quot;&gt;identi.ca&lt;/a&gt; back in the Twitter #failwhale days. It never caught on for various reasons. Today we have two other choices &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.net&quot;&gt;app.net&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://tent.io/&quot;&gt;Tent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;App.net made the first big splash with a unique funding method, ask your end users to fund you. App.net philosophy is pure it simple make the backbone for the developers to build off of and make the end user the consumer not the product. It is a pay to play platform which will keep many away. At the same time I think that will help the service scale and allow for developers to build unique and interesting services for the next few years. The Twitter like functionality (alpha) is just a quaint fundraising side show.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have &lt;a href=&quot;http://tent.io/&quot;&gt;Tent&lt;/a&gt;. However, unlike App.net, tent isn’t a platform, its a protocol for social networking. Not only that it is decentralized, which will ensure it stay open. Yet that brings upon it many problems such as long term interoperability. It isn’t a service nor is it a platform, but idea how social networking should function. I have high hope for the tent &lt;a href=&quot;https://tent.is/&quot;&gt;status app, tent.is&lt;/a&gt; and hope it takes off. I however feel it has many growing pains ahead, the potential user base already has ideas and expectations. The status app must either evolve meet those expectations or refine itself to show the user a better way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course these are my quick thoughts and haven’t really spent much time looking App.net or Tent. I like what I see with Tent, so &lt;a href=&quot;https://mitchejj.tent.is/&quot;&gt;signed up&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;https://tent.is/&quot;&gt;tent.is&lt;/a&gt;. And the tent github wiki has a nice page &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/tent/tent.io/wiki/Explaining-Tent&quot;&gt;Explaining Tent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Wallpaper</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/09/21/wallpaper/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-21T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/09/21/wallpaper</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I found my new homescreen background.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>This Can't be Good</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/09/19/this-cant-be-good/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-19T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/09/19/this-cant-be-good</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Part of a crash log report that caused my iPhone not to sync last night:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Crashed Thread:  0  Dispatch queue: com.apple.main-thread

Exception Type:  EXC_BAD_ACCESS (SIGBUS)
Exception Codes: KERN_PROTECTION_FAILURE at 0x0000000100700000

VM Regions Near 0x100700000:
    MALLOC_TINY            0000000100600000-0000000100700000 [ 1024K] rw-/rwx SM=PRV  
--&amp;gt; STACK GUARD            0000000100700000-0000000100701000 [    4K] ---/rwx SM=NUL  stack guard for thread 1
    Stack                  0000000100701000-0000000100783000 [  520K] rw-/rwx SM=COW  thread 1

Thread 0 Crashed:: Dispatch queue: com.apple.main-thread
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Run Mate</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/review/2012/09/17/run-mate/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/review/2012/09/17/run-mate</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;When I first started to run I would run excessive at the gym, indoors on a treadmill. The idea of running outside, where the elements and nature could interfere with my feeble attempt at running horrified me. I knew I need help to start running, couch to 5k apps where all the rage. They where all relatively cheap and similarly priced at $2.99. I knew I would eventually outgrow the 5k apps, as I was targeting completing a half-marathon. If I could find a training app that would aid in my endeavor I would be happy, I found such an app, &lt;a href=&quot;http://itunes.apple.com/app/run-mate/id322005319&quot;&gt;Run Mate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would not generally classify Run Mate as useful app away from a treadmill, but I may be wrong. I’ve since moved on to other tools as I dread running indoors and the bulk of my running takes place outdoors. At the core, Run Mate is a powerful, albeit, fickle utility. The User Interface shows some thought was give to the end user, Yet the UX is rough around the corners and implemented in the most vexing ways, that eventually grow tiresome. If you choose to use Run Mate, ignore sound prompts and rely solely on the voice overs. Also, avoid all temptation to pick up your iOS device to multitask or change tracks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A user can easily create a training routine that fits their goals. I wanted to running an interval set using the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/High-intensity_interval_training#Little_method&quot;&gt;Little Method&lt;/a&gt; this evening at the gym. I quickly configure a training plan before stepping on the treadmill, six minutes in I wondered why the first prompt had yet to fire. I checked the Run Mate, and sure enough it was on step four. I forgot that the sound prompts are essentially nonexistent, I changed the plan to use the dread voice prompts and started over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fact I’ve never once heard a sound prompt from Run Mate until later in the evening after a podcast I was listing to ended. My eyes wondering where wondering the computer screen and I heard these faint repetitive pings in the distant background. It was then I my ear buds where still affixed to my ears and my podcast was over. When I removed one bud the sound was isolated to the other ear. Odd, killing the process halted the pings, starting a run started the pings again. So yes, not only are the sound prompts faint and nonexistent the are also unreliable.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Complete Guide to Interval Training</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/fitness/2012/09/17/interval-training/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/fitness/2012/09/17/interval-training</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I was listing podcast the other day where they where talking about HIIT, High Intensity Interval Training.; more specifically the Tabata and Little Methods. I wasn’t able to sleep last night and figured I would look into the Little Method more. Only to find the infographic above from the same source I linked to the other day, &lt;a href=&quot;http://greatist.com/&quot;&gt;http://greatist.com/&lt;/a&gt;, they my soon have a place in my daily reading line up. Oh, and I plan on using Little Method when I visit the gym for a short 30 minute run this evening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The protocol calls for 60 seconds of high intensity followed by 75 seconds of low intensity. Repeat for a total of 12 cycles (totaling 27 minutes) up to three times per week.
&lt;small&gt;&lt;cite&gt;greatist.com&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Fitbit & The Zip</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/fitness/2012/09/17/fitbit-the-zip/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-17T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/fitness/2012/09/17/fitbit-the-zip</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I ordered my first &lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/fitbit/classic/&quot;&gt;fitbit, the classic,&lt;/a&gt; on March 8th 2010, each day I wait in anticipation for production to ramp up. Finally on May 18th my fitbit shipped. Sadly my fitbit died a few month later, as I completed my first half marathon. I found out the hard way the fitbit wasn’t water resistant at all. The fitbit also didn’t seem very durable construction wise, but I didn’t exactly wear it as directed. I’m sure that contributed to my original failing. Last year jawbone released their failed entry into the space, with the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jawbone.com/up/&quot;&gt;Jawbone UP&lt;/a&gt; shortly after that Nike announced their &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nike%2B_FuelBand&quot;&gt;FuelBand&lt;/a&gt;. Each of those items had something the I wanted in the fitbit before making a replacement purchase, Bluetooth syncing to my phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Fitbit Zip is a low-cost Fitbit that tracks steps, distance, and calories burned, syncing the results to your computer or smartphone. The Zip also features a friendly touch display to check your stats, and has a user-replaceable battery that lasts up to six months each time.
&lt;small&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/fitbit/zip/&quot;&gt;gdgt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, fitbit announced two new products the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fitbit.com/one&quot;&gt;One&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fitbit.com/zip&quot;&gt;Zip&lt;/a&gt;. Both promise to sync via &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bluetooth#Bluetooth_v4.0&quot;&gt;Bluetooth 4.0&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bluetooth_low_energy&quot;&gt;Bluetooth Smart&lt;/a&gt;, and both are said to be water resistant (sweat,rain and the like). I really wanted to buy the One, but two things held me back. First, its pre-shipping order status and second the design looks similar enough to the original created a love-hate connection in my mind. While the Zip had one negative in my book, no sleep tracking. I placed an order for my Zip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If you want to turn fitness into a lifestyle, the One is for you. For starters, it never rests. During the day, it tracks your steps, distance, calories burned, and stairs climbed. Come nightfall, it measures your sleep cycle, helps you learn how to sleep better, and wakes you in the morning. The One motivates you to reach your goals by bringing greater fitness into your life – seamlessly, socially, 24 hours a day.
&lt;small&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://gdgt.com/fitbit/one/&quot;&gt;gdgt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; after an outing at the gym I put my order on hold. I don’t think I have the same use case for a fitbit I did back in 2010. Going with a product that is less than the orginal may not be a wise buying choice. I will wait and see product review of both the Zip and One before buy.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>The Ultimate Runner’s Guide</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/fitness/2012/09/15/the-ultimate-runners-guide/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/fitness/2012/09/15/the-ultimate-runners-guide</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>iPhone5 Blueprints</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/link/2012/09/15/iphone5-blueprints/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/link/2012/09/15/iphone5-blueprints</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Isn’t it nice Apple has posted the exact dimensions for the cases makers? I’m not buying an iPhone5 myself anytime soon, however I just found the blueprints nifty.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Running Check List</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/09/12/running-check-list/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/09/12/running-check-list</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;div class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
  &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.strongspace.com/shared/yaeqregpre/img/Race_Day_Checklist.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-rounded img-post&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>iPhone X</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/09/11/iphone-x/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-11T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/09/11/iphone-x</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;It is that time of year when Apple is poised to release yet another version of the iPhone. I recall my first &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iphone&quot;&gt;iPhone&lt;/a&gt;, the orginal, which I beat up fairly well. I bought it with the intent of jailbreaking it and running it of T-Mobile. I upgraded to the 3G a year later but this time I opted to sign up for an AT&amp;amp;T contract. When the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iphone_4&quot;&gt;iPhone 4&lt;/a&gt; came out the 3G was slugish and I loved the ascetic look of the 4 and yes I did upgrade to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Iphone_4s&quot;&gt;iPhone 4S&lt;/a&gt;, mostly for well I don’t know &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bluetooth#Bluetooth_v4.0&quot;&gt;Bluetooth 4.0&lt;/a&gt;. When Apple first announced the 4 I really couldn’t think of anything else I would want in a phone, err, pocket sized handheld mobile computer. So what could the iPhone [5s/6] offer that would compel me to upgrade again next year? I am nearly certain the iPhone 5 will sport LTE, improved processing power, improved camera and a new dock port. The geek in me is looking forward to LTE, I didn’t want it last year, and I always welcome improved processing power. Dock ports, I honestly don’t care one way of the other, and I really don’t take enough pictures to really care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s left for the 2013 iPhone? Processor/RAM/battery improvements. &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Near_Field_Communication&quot;&gt;NFC&lt;/a&gt;? That sound grand but would I find it useful in daily life? I know I would love to have less to carry around with me. However would enough terminals exist in my daily life that honor the Apple version of NFC? Doubtful. Would I really use the NFC bits in the phone if I can’t use it on a regular basis? Very unlikely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t wait to see what is announced tomorrow, nor can wait for the 2013 speculation to begin.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Giving Back</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/09/04/giving-back/"/>
   <updated>2012-09-04T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/09/04/giving-back</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I the course of building and deploying this site one particular site has been truly helpful, Stack Overflow. Today I was finally able to give back and answer a fairly simple question that had me perplex when I first encountered it, &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12241403/jekyll-on-heroku-listing-additional-internal-posts-i-havent-created&quot;&gt;Jekyll on Heroku listing additional (internal?) posts I haven’t created&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The probelm:&lt;/strong&gt; Jekyll on heroku publishes mysterious pages, and they all relate to your project someway, somehow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The solution:&lt;/strong&gt; Let’s call the directory where Jekyll is installed &amp;amp; running from the root /. Heroku installs the applications gems in &lt;code&gt;/vendor&lt;/code&gt;. When Jekyll builds the site it scans all files and folder in the root file directory, including &lt;code&gt;/vendor&lt;/code&gt;.  Fix is to simple edit &lt;code&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; and put ‘vendor’ in the exclude array.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>quick and dirty metrics</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/08/26/quick-and-dirty-metrics/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/08/26/quick-and-dirty-metrics</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Now that I have github -&amp;gt; heroku publishing in place now is the time to setup even more over kill, heroku offers a few (2)5 MB Memcache Bucket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I made the following changes to &lt;code&gt;config.ru&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;	if memcache_servers = ENV[&quot;MEMCACHE_SERVERS&quot;]
		require &#39;dalli&#39;
		require &#39;rack-cache&#39;
		require &#39;memcachier&#39;
		$cache = Dalli::Client.new
		use Rack::Cache,
			:verbose =&amp;gt; true,
			:metastore =&amp;gt; $cache,
			:entitystore =&amp;gt; $cache
	end
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To test that caching is working use &lt;code&gt;ab&lt;/code&gt; aka Apache HTTP server benchmarking tool and run &lt;code&gt;ab -n 500 -c 5 [hostname]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will make 500 requst to [hostname] with 5 concurrent request.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And to see if &lt;code&gt;Rack::Deflater&lt;/code&gt; is working&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;	curl -I -H &quot;Accept-Encoding: gzip,deflate&quot; [hostname]
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>github to heroku deplyment</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/blog/2012/08/26/github-to-heroku-deplyment/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/blog/2012/08/26/github-to-heroku-deplyment</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Once again I’m taking inspiration from Jonas Forsberg and &lt;a href=&quot;http://jonasforsberg.se/2012/07/29/deploy-to-heroku-from-github&quot;&gt;Deploy to Heroku from Github&lt;/a&gt;. However, I just couln’t get the thing to work. So I backtracked to the orginal project &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ajlai/github-heroku-pusher&quot;&gt;github-heroku-pusher&lt;/a&gt; and everything now seems to be in working order. I think I will circle back around to his method eventually, but for now, while I build out the site I’m going to follow the don’t fix what isn’t broken mantra.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So for now no more ‘git push heroku master’… unless I’m fiddling with some config settings and something breaks…&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Create a Post or Page</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/08/26/create-a-post-or-page/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/08/26/create-a-post-or-page</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Why is it I can never remember:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;	rake post title=&quot;Hello World&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre lang=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;	rake page name=&quot;about.md&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>test_video</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_video/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_video</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>test_text</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_text/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_text</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;h4 id=&quot;section&quot;&gt;1&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insipidity the sufficient discretion imprudence resolution sir him decisively. Proceed how any engaged visitor. Explained propriety off out perpetual his you. Feel sold off felt nay rose met you. We so entreaties cultivated astonished is. Was sister for few longer mrs sudden talent become. Done may bore quit evil old mile. If likely am of beauty tastes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possession her thoroughly remarkably terminated man continuing. Removed greater to do ability. You shy shall while but wrote marry. Call why sake has sing pure. Gay six set polite nature worthy. So matter be me we wisdom should basket moment merely. Me burst ample wrong which would mr he could. Visit arise my point timed drawn no. Can friendly laughter goodness man him appetite carriage. Any widen see gay forth alone fruit bed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not far stuff she think the jokes. Going as by do known noise he wrote round leave. Warmly put branch people narrow see. Winding its waiting yet parlors married own feeling. Marry fruit do spite jokes an times. Whether at it unknown warrant herself winding if. Him same none name sake had post love. An busy feel form hand am up help. Parties it brother amongst an fortune of. Twenty behind wicket why age now itself ten. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boy favourable day can introduced sentiments entreaties. Noisier carried of in warrant because. So mr plate seems cause chief widen first. Two differed husbands met screened his. Bed was form wife out ask draw. Wholly coming at we no enable. Offending sir delivered questions now new met. Acceptance she interested new boisterous day discretion celebrated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good draw knew bred ham busy his hour. Ask agreed answer rather joy nature admire wisdom. Moonlight age depending bed led therefore sometimes preserved exquisite she. An fail up so shot leaf wise in. Minuter highest his arrived for put and. Hopes lived by rooms oh in no death house. Contented direction september but end led excellent ourselves may. Ferrars few arrival his offered not charmed you. Offered anxious respect or he. On three thing chief years in money arise of. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Effect if in up no depend seemed. Ecstatic elegance gay but disposed. We me rent been part what. An concluded sportsman offending so provision mr education. Bed uncommonly his discovered for estimating far. Equally he minutes my hastily. Up hung mr we give rest half. Painful so he an comfort is manners. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add you viewing ten equally believe put. Separate families my on drawings do oh offended strictly elegance. Perceive jointure be mistress by jennings properly. An admiration at he discovered difficulty continuing. We in building removing possible suitable friendly on. Nay middleton him admitting consulted and behaviour son household. Recurred advanced he oh together entrance speedily suitable. Ready tried gay state fat could boy its among shall. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tiled say decay spoil now walls meant house. My mr interest thoughts screened of outweigh removing. Evening society musical besides inhabit ye my. Lose hill well up will he over on. Increasing sufficient everything men him admiration unpleasing sex. Around really his use uneasy longer him man. His our pulled nature elinor talked now for excuse result. Admitted add peculiar get joy doubtful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lose john poor same it case do year we. Full how way even the sigh. Extremely nor furniture fat questions now provision incommode preserved. Our side fail find like now. Discovered travelling for insensible partiality unpleasing impossible she. Sudden up my excuse to suffer ladies though or. Bachelor possible marianne directly confined relation as on he. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To shewing another demands to. Marianne property cheerful informed at striking at. Clothes parlors however by cottage on. In views it or meant drift to. Be concern parlors settled or do shyness address. Remainder northward performed out for moonlight. Yet late add name was rent park from rich. He always do do former he highly.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>test_quote</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_quote/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_quote</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The secret to creativity is knowing how to hide your sources. 
&lt;small&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.quotedb.com/quotes/2112&quot;&gt;Albert Einstein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>test_picture</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_picture/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/test/2012/08/13/test_picture</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;div class=&quot;image&quot;&gt;
  &lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.huffpost.com/gen/549299/original.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-rounded img-post&quot; /&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Mon Aug 13</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/08/13/mon-aug-13/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-13T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/08/13/mon-aug-13</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;I’m using a combination of &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/textmate/textmate&quot;&gt;TextMate&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.barebones.com/products/textwrangler/index.shtml&quot;&gt;TextWrangler&lt;/a&gt; to create and edit post along with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.panic.com/coda/&quot;&gt;Coda 2&lt;/a&gt; craft the design of the site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a helpful modification to the TextMate markdown bundle,&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>prose.io</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/08/09/proseio/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/08/09/proseio</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Prose is a web-based interface for managing text-based content in your GitHub repositories. Use it to create, edit, and delete files, and save your changes directly to GitHub.
&lt;small&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://prose.io/&quot;&gt;Prose&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>heroku</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/08/09/heroku/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/08/09/heroku</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;After playing with jekyll on Git Hub’s pages, I realized I needed something with a bit more zest. I needed plug-in support. I found Jonas Forsberg post entitled &lt;a href=&quot;http://jonasforsberg.se/2012/07/22/jekyll-heroku-unicorn&quot;&gt;Jekyll + Heroku + Unicorn = Blazing fast blogging&lt;/a&gt; and basically followed the step outlined below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo gem install heroku&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;sudo gem install bundler&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;heroku auth:login&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;git clone git@github.com:himynameisjonas/jekyll-heroku-unicorn.git&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;cd jekyll-heroku-unicorn&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;bundle install&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;heroku create&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;git push heroku master&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That lead to a complete fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Running: bundle install --without development:test --path vendor/bundle --binstubs bin/ --deployment
You are trying to install in deployment mode after changing
your Gemfile. Run `bundle install` elsewhere and add the
updated Gemfile.lock to version control.
You have added to the Gemfile:
* source: https://github.com/adaoraul/ra... (at master)
You have deleted from the Gemfile:
* source: git://github.com/adaoraul/rack... (at master)
You have changed in the Gemfile:
* rack-jekyll from `https://github.com/adaoraul/ra... (at master)` to `no specified source`
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time to regroup, I searched around and found a nice how-to guide, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thomas.stachl.me/blog/2012/05/26/jekyll-on-heroku.html&quot;&gt;Jekyll on Heroku&lt;/a&gt; by Thomas Stachl. It seem straight forward, yet it to failed. I looked around some more, and found &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mikemayo.org/2012/deploying-jekyll-sites-to-heroku-with-rack-jekyll&quot;&gt;Deploying Jekyll sites to Heroku with Rack-Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; which gave two little snippets of code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;gem &#39;rack-jekyll&#39;, :git =&amp;gt; &#39;https://github.com/adaoraul/rack-jekyll.git&#39;, :require =&amp;gt; &#39;rack/jekyll&#39;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;require &#39;bundler&#39;
Bundler.require(:default, :production)

run Rack::Jekyll.new
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ah-ha, why not meld all of this goodness together. Drat, another failure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Heroku push rejected, no Cedar-supported app detected
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hmmm, thinking… Eureka! Wait bundler isn’t the app I wish to deploy…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My new config.ru file&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;require &#39;bundler&#39;
require &quot;rack/jekyll&quot;
Bundler.require(:default, :production)

run Rack::Jekyll.new(:destination =&amp;gt; &#39;public&#39;)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Gemfile&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;source :rubygems

gem &quot;rake&quot;                # actually not need for heroku but for the provided Rakefile
gem &quot;RedCloth&quot;            # if you want to use the Textile Markup Language
#gem &quot;jekyll&quot;, &quot;~&amp;gt; 0.11.2&quot; # we need at least this version so jekyll will use Ruby 1.9.2
gem &#39;rack-jekyll&#39;, :git =&amp;gt; &#39;https://github.com/adaoraul/rack-jekyll.git&#39;, :require =&amp;gt; &#39;rack/jekyll&#39;
#gem &quot;foreman&quot;             # this is a tool to test and use the Procfile locally
gem &quot;heroku&quot;              # if you install the Heroku Toolbelt you won&#39;t need this but it&#39;s good practice
gem &#39;unicorn&#39;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Procfile&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;web: bundle exec unicorn -p $PORT -c ./unicorn.rb
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My unicorn.rb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;worker_processes 4 # amount of unicorn workers to spin up
timeout 30         # restarts workers that hang for 30 seconds
preload_app true   # avoid regeneration of jekyll site for each fork
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I deployed the app in the cloud had some curious extra data. I noticed I also forgot to included a Procfile file. I added the relevant lines redeployed the app and now I just crash. One wobbly step forward. After some thought, I noticed I forgot to include the unicorn config file. #fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;coderay&quot;&gt;coderay&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose you use &lt;code&gt;coderay_css: style&lt;/code&gt; to stylize code, this provides for inline styling. Since I dnon’t plan on providing much code examples on the site, so I don’t want to server up that style sheet all the time. However, if your planning on having alot of code snippits &lt;code&gt;coderay_css: css&lt;/code&gt; is your option and generate your style sheet via &lt;code&gt;coderay stylesheet &amp;gt; coderay.css&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;prerequisites&quot;&gt;Prerequisites&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xcode – Xcode -&amp;gt; Preferences -&amp;gt; Downlads -&amp;gt; Install Command Line Tools&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;ruby &amp;lt;(curl -fsSk https://raw.github.com/mxcl/homebrew/go)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;brew install git&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gem update --system&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gem install jekyll&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gem install bundler&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;gem install heroku&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Hello World</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/2012/08/07/hello-world/"/>
   <updated>2012-08-07T00:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/2012/08/07/hello-world</id>
   <content type="html">
&lt;p&gt;Nothing to see here, yet. Just another amoeba learning to walk, look lively as you exit on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>test_video</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/test/2011/12/13/test_video/"/>
   <updated>2011-12-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/test/2011/12/13/test_video</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>test_video</title>
   <link href="http://stderr.me/test/2011/02/13/test_video/"/>
   <updated>2011-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://stderr.me/test/2011/02/13/test_video</id>
   <content type="html">
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>